

Portfolio

This resume as a website I made
My GitHub profile
My Scrum.org profile

Contacts

Phone: +48 725 135 671 E-mail: rogulskaannamaria@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Anna-Maria Rogulska

Tech skills and tools

- Salesforce: Sales Cloud |
 Salesforce Inspector,
 Salesforce Workbench
- HTML & CSS
- PostgreSQL | PGAdmin
- MySQL | MySQL Workbench
- GIT | Bitbucket, GitHub, GitLab
- REST API | Postman
- TestLink
- Jira

Now learning

· Cypress | Cypress Cloud

Soft skills

- Agile & Scrum
- Good communicator
- Facilitation
- Teamwork
- Proficient in English & French

Anna-Maria Rogulska

OA specialist with Scrum

I am a software QA specialist with 3-year experience and a scrum enthusiast.

I worked on several international projects, both leading and supporting the quality assurance process in the software development lifecycle, as well as participating in building a sustainable agile environment.

In my work I focus on **precision** and **good communication**. My favourite element of the software development process is the **value** we bring to the customer as a **team**.

Employment history

QA / tester at ROCKWOOL Group

December 2021 - now

- Creating, managing and executing test suites according to functional and non-functional requirements
- Managing the QA processes, including designing & continuously improving procedures
- Facilitating creation and development of a test autiomation project
- Co-designing and conducting an agile transformation

Software tester at DAC Software Polska

December 2019 - November 2021

- Defining test scenarios based on business requirements
- Conducting manual tests (UI, integration, other)
- Taking active part in **feature design** process
- Supporting the development team as a Scrum Master

Education & certifications

Information Technology - bachelor programme, Collegium Da Vinci

October 2021 - now

ISTQB Foundation Level Agile Tester, | CERTIFICATE

January 2023

Professional Scrum Master II, Scrum.org | CERTIFICATE

December 2022

Professional Scrum Master I, Scrum.org | CERTIFICATE

September 2020

ISTQB Foundation Level | CERTIFICATE

August 2020

Hobbies

music production, a capella, choir arrangements, solo singing, DIY

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the software quality assurance, software test automation and agile-related positions, as well as for relevant future recruitment processes within those fields of work.